&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好的，欢迎从强制练习中回来。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay, welcome back from the coercion exercise.
希望你发现这是一个有趣的挑战。
Hopefully you found that an interesting challenge.
让我们再次开始，记住read me说我们需要一个is valid name函数。
Let's start, again, remember the read me says we want an is valid name function.
因此，我们将从定义isValidName()开始。
So we'll start by defining isValidName().
它需要一个名称，它需要断言几个东西。
It needs to take a name, and it needs to assert several things.
首先，它是一个字符串。
First off, that it is a string.
其次，它至少包含一些不仅仅是空白的东西，
Secondly, that it contains at least something that's not only white space,
并且它包含的不是空白的内容至少必须是
and the stuff that it contains that's not white space has to be at least
三个字符长，好吗？
three characters long, okay?
因此，首先，我们要确保typeof name=“string”。
So first off, we wanna make sure that the typeof name == "string".
在这里，我将双等号与运算符的类型一起使用，因为我们
Here I'm using the double equals with the type of operator because we
知道运算符的类型总是返回字符串。
know that the type of operator always returns strings.
我们知道它总是返回非空字符串，
And we know that it always returns non-empty strings,
所以我们知道，如果你愿意的话，我们已经安全地走出了角落的箱子。
so we know we're safely out of the corner cases, if you will.
因此如果(typeof name=“string”)，
So if (typeof name == "string"),
还有，&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我们也想
and, &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: We also wanna
确保我们不会只考虑字符串中可能存在的任何空白，
make sure that we don't consider any only white space that may be in the string,
在我们的长度检查方面，也就是说。
in terms of our length check, that is.
因此，使用JavaScript字符串实现这一点的一个内置方法是trim方法。
So one built-in way to do that with JavaScript strings is the trim method.
所以我们可以说if name.trim()，它可以修剪掉任何权重空间
So we can say if name.trim(), which trims off any weight space
从两边，如果剩下的长度至少是3，
from either side, and if what is left is at least of length three,
那么我们就知道我们有一个有效的字符串。
then we know we have a valid string.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我使用的是大于，还是大于或等于？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Did I use greater than, or greater than or equal?
是的，对不起，&gt；=3，好吗？
Yeah, I'm sorry, &gt;= 3, okay?
在这种情况下，我们希望返回TRUE，否则可以返回FALSE。
In that case, we wanna return true, and otherwise we can return false.
现在，您可以将其简化为简单地
Now, you could simplify this a little bit to simply
如果这是您的偏好，请返回该表达式。
return that expression if that's your preference.
这里不能有if语句。
You could not have an if statement here.
只是为了说明我们所做的决定，
Just being illustrative of the decision making that we make,
我们处于成功状态是什么？
which is are we in a success condition?
很好，我们返回TRUE，否则我们不是，并且我们返回FALSE。
Great, we return true, otherwise we're not, and we return false.
所以如果我们现在就测试一下，我们应该让测试通过，并且
So if we just test this right away, we should get that test to pass, and
我们应该通过这六个测试，其他的都应该失败。
we should get these six tests to pass, and everything else should fail.
我不想出错，所以我只想定义
I don't wanna get errors, so I'm gonna just define
一个hoursAttendant()，并让它不为我们返回任何内容。
an hoursAttended() and have it return nothing for us.
所以其余的都应该失败。
So all the rest of those should fail.
所以让我们试试，&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：在控制台上。
So let's try, &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Over in the console.
同样，您可以通过Node运行它，如果您觉得更舒服的话。
Again, you could run that via Node, if that feels more comfortable to you.
但是让我们在控制台上运行它，并且
But let's run it over here in the console, and
让我们看看它是否打印出我们期望的结果。
let's see if it prints out the results we're expecting.
所以第一个测试返回TRUE，这很好，然后我们有几个失败。
So the first test returns true, which is good, and then we have several failures.
四次失败，然后我们有一，二，三，四，五，六次成功，所以
Four failures, and then we have one, two, three, four, five, six successes, so
我们看到有效的名字通过了我们的测试三，好吗？
we see that is valid name is passing our test three, okay?
这是很好的进展。
That's good progress.
让我们转到小时关注。
Let's move on to hoursAttended.
现在，这个稍微复杂一点，但不是很明显，
Now, this one was a little bit more complex but not significantly so,
它接受两个参数。
it takes in two parameters.
记住我们将呼叫那些出席的人，意思是你的小时数
Remember we're gonna call those attended, meaning the number of hours that you
参加了一个研讨会，以及研讨会的长度。
attended a workshop, and the length of the workshop.
现在，我们正在努力确保输入的内容是有效的，
Now, we're trying to make sure that what was inputted is valid,
你参加的时间不超过研讨会实际参加的时间，
that you attended not more hours than the workshop actually attended,
你不会想在那里得到额外的学分的。
you don't wanna get extra credit there.
所以Read Me说我们要确保这些是字符串或数字，
So the read me says we wanna make sure that these are either strings or numbers,
不管他们是哪一个我们都会把他们当成数字。
and that regardless of which one they are we're gonna treat them as numbers.
所以如果Attended是一个字符串，那么我们想把它变成一个数字，好吗？
So if the attended is a string then we wanna turn it into a number, okay?
因此，首先我们可以说如果(typeof attended=“string”)。
So first off we could say if the (typeof attended == "string").
你还记得它会的，我会在这里再检查一遍。
And you recall that it's going to, I'll just double check here.
是的，我们记得我们需要确保
Yep, we recall that we need to make sure
我们不会把空字符串强制为零，
that we're not getting an empty string coerced into a zero,
因为这和有人在这里键入零不是一回事。
cuz that's not the same thing as somebody typing in zero here.
所以这就是我们想要处理的一个小角落的案子。
So that's a little corner case that we wanna take care of.
所以我们要说的是如果服务员的类型是字符串，并且
So we're gonna say if type of attendant is a string, and
我们又要用我们的小朋友修剪了。
we're gonna use our little friend trim again.
Attended.trim()不等于空字符串。
And attended.trim() is not equal to empty string.
因此，我们不希望这里只有任何空白或空字符串。
So we don't want any white space only or empty strings to fit in here.
但是如果我们有一个非空字符串，那么让我们继续
But if we have a non-empty string, then let's go ahead and
试着把它变成一个数字。
try to make it into a number.
所以在这里我们可以说Attended=number(Attended)。
So here we could say attended = Number(attended).
现在，这就是我与标准人群的一些不同之处，例如，
Now, here's where I diverge a bit from standard crowd that, for example,
像静态类型一样，因为他们不喜欢将变量重新分配给它的新类型。
like static typing, cuz they don't like to reassign a variable to its new type.
我认为这是用不同的
I think this is a perfectly valid example of reassigning variables with a different
类型，当您出于某种目的显式更改类型时，就像我们在这里一样。
type, when you are explicitly changing the type for some purpose, like we are here.
所以这就是为什么
So that's one of the reasons why
我不喜欢工具抱怨我重新分配类型。
I don't like it when tools complain at me about reassigning over types.
好的，我们要做和刚才参加的一样的事情，
Okay, so we're gonna do the same thing that we just did for attended,
我们也想对长度变量这样做。
we also wanna do that for the length variable.
所以我将复制它，并将变量更改为length。
So I will just duplicate that and change the variable to length.
我们可能会把它分解成一个函数，但[声音]谁在乎呢？
We could probably factor that out into a function, but [SOUND] who cares?
好的，现在我们知道了，如果它是以字符串的形式传入的，那么它就变成了一个数字。
Okay, so now we know that if it was passed in as a string, it has become a number.
如果它是一个数字，它仍然是一个数字。
If it was a number, it's still a number.
但我们不知道您是否传入了类似null或
But we don't know that you might have passed in something like null or
未定义，所以我们实际上仍然需要检查这两个数字
undefined, so we still actually need to check that both of these are numbers
在我们做什么之前。
before we do something.
所以我们的支票意味着首先说，
So our check means to first say,
如果typeof attended=“number”
if typeof attended == "number"
&amp；&amp；typeof length=“number”。
&amp;&amp; typeof length == "number".
如果这两个都不是真的，我们就会跳伞，对吧？
If either one of those is not true, we're gonna bail out, right?
这是我们的if语句，并且
So here is our if statement, and
然后我们会跳伞，这意味着我们最终会返回错误。
then we're gonna bail out, and that means we end up returning false.
这个没有通过验证。
This didn't pass the validation.
但除了事实之外，我们还需要检查更多
But there's more that we need to check besides just the fact
它们是数字。
that they are numbers.
如果你回想起读我这本书，
If you recall in the read me,
它说我们要确保他们被当作数字对待。
it said we wanna make sure that they're treated as numbers.
它们必须为0或更高。
They need to be 0 or higher.
所以我们不仅要检查它们是不是数字，
So we need to check not only that they are numbers,
但我们还需要看到attended&gt；=0，length&gt；=0。
but we need to also see that attended &gt;= 0, and length &gt;= 0.
Read Me还说它们需要是整数，
The read me also says that they need to be whole numbers,
这意味着它们不能像测试用例中那样是3.14或9.1。
meaning they can't be like 3.14, or 9.1 as in the test cases.
因此，如果您对MDN进行了快速检查，您可能会发现
So if you did a quick check on mdn you might have found that
JavaScript中有一个专门为此而构建的实用程序。
there is a utility built into JavaScript specially for this.
它叫做Number.isInteger，它告诉我们是否有东西，是吗？
And it's called Number.isInteger, that tells us if we have a thing that is, yeah?
&gt；&gt；演讲者2：我的意思是，我认为你实际上把它作为第一个数字
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: I mean, I think you actually casted it as a number in the first
一部分对吧？
part, right?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：SO
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yes. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So
它们以后可能永远都是数字[CROSSTALK]
they're are always gonna be numbers afterwards probably [CROSSTALK]
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：他们是，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: They are,
因为如果我在这里传递一个NULL，那么它就不会进入这个子句
because if I pass in a null here then it's not gonna go into this clause and
这里仍然是空的。
it's gonna still be null here.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：嗯哼。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Uh-huh.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所以这就是为什么我必须检查
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So that's why I have to check to
确保它确实是一个数字。
make sure that it's actually a number.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：对，因为我们希望允许字符串和数字，但是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Right, cuz we want to allow strings and numbers, but
如果你传入任何其他东西，你将会通过验证，如果你会的话。
if you pass in anything else, you're gonna fail the validation, if you will.
传递NULL将使验证失败。
Passing a null fails the validation.
好的，所以我们要检查一下，以确保Attended实际上是一个整数。
Okay, so we're gonna check to make sure that attended is actually an integer.
我们要检查一下，&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：长度是
And we're gonna check that, &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Length is
实际上是一个整数。
actually an integer.
它实际上只是说它上面没有任何小数成分，
That really literally just says doesn't have any fractional component on it,
基本上就是它在做什么，对吧？
basically what it's doing, right?
所以检查它是不是一个整数，好吗？
So checking that it's a whole number, all right?
然后最后一件事，读我说
And then the final thing that the read me says
出席的人必须小于或等于长度。
is that attended has to be less than or equal to length.
好吧，因为我们肯定知道我们处理的是格式良好的数字
Well, since we definitely know we're dealing with well formed numbers at this
点，我们没有任何nans，或无穷大，或任何其他东西。
point, we don't have any NaNs, or infinities, or any of that other stuff.
那么对我们来说这是一个非常安全的检查，Attended&lt；=length。
Then it's a very safe check for us to say, attended &lt;= length.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所以我们限制了可以
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So we've restricted the overall surface area that could
可能会让我们陷入困境。
have possibly gotten us into corner cases.
到什么是一组相当直接的检查来验证
Into what is a fairly straightforward set of checks to validate
我们所传递的就是我们想要被传递的。
that what we're passing in is what we want to be passed in.
我们正在消除任何一个角落的案子，
And we're eliminating any of those corner cases,
比如有人传入了一个包含数字的数组，或者
like somebody passed in an array with a number in it or
任何其他像那样疯狂的事，好吗？
anything else bonkers like that, okay?
如果我们通过了所有这些检查，那么我们可以返回TRUE，
If we have passed all of these checks then we can return true,
如果没有通过，那么我们可以返回FALSE。
and if that didn't pass, then we can return false.
和以前一样，
Same thing as before,
现在我们可以将其重构为一个返回语句。
we could now refactor that to a single return statement.
我只是想让你了解我们是如何构建这些测试用例的，好吗？
I just wanted you to get the point of how we build up those test cases, okay?
现在让我们在控制台中测试此代码，
So let's now test this code over in our console,
我们现在应该拿到所有的真货，所以
and we should get all trues now, so
运行这段代码，我们就会得到所有的真值，耶。
run this code and we get all trues, yay.
好的，我们已经编写了几个验证器函数，
All right, so we've written a couple of validator functions,
想让你熟悉这个想法
point being wanted to get you familiar with the idea
使用这些原始值以及它们可以被强迫的方式。
working with these primitive values and the ways that they can be coerced.
仍然不会偏离轨道进入那些疯狂的角落案件。
And still not go off the rails into those crazy corner cases.
保护自己免受那些角落案件的侵袭。
Protect yourself against those corner cases.
当然，有很多方法可以实现这两种方法中的任何一种
There are of course lots of ways that you could have implemented either one of these
函数。
functions.
而不是做一个.length或检查一些东西，
Instead of doing a .length or checking for something,
您可以使用正则表达式。
you could have used a regular expression.
但它的精神是利用我们所知道的原始类型和
But the spirit of this was to use what we know about primitive types and
关于我们强制说的支票，好吗？
about the checks that our coercion say, okay?